ACTWU's Murray Finley Records from the President's Office 5619/036
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Amalgamated Services and Allied Forces Joint Board, 1975-1976 (Box 10, Folder 7)
- AFL-CIO Executive Council, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 8)
- AFL-CIO Executive Council, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 9)
- AFL-CIO Executive Council, 1975-1976 (Box 10, Folder 10)
- Clothing Negotiations, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 11)
- Clothing Negotiations, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 12)
- Business/Labor Working Group, 1976-1977 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Business. Labor Working Group, 1976 (Box 11, Folder 2)
- Business. Labor Working Group, 1976 (Box 11, Folder 3)
- Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union, 1975-1976 (Box 11, Folder 4)
- Women`s Coalition of Labor Union, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 5)
- Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  clips
- Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers, 1976 (Box 11, Folder 7)
- ACTWU, 1976-1977 (Box 11, Folder 8)
- Ratification of Settlement with CMA, 1976 (Box 11, Folder 9)
- Clothing Negotiations, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 10)
- Clothing Negotiations, 1974 (Box 12, Folder 1)
- Clothing Negotiations, 1974 (Box 12, Folder 2)
- Textile Merger, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 3)
- Textile Merger, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 4)
- Textile Merger, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 5)
- Textile Merger, 1973-1974 (Box 12, Folder 6)
- Textile Merger, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 7)
- Textile Merger, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 8)
- Textile Merger, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 9)
- Textile Merger, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 10)
- Textile Merger, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 11)
- Urban Community Insurance Company, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 12)
- Urban Community Insurance Company, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 13)
- 1974 Convention (Box 13, Folder 1)
- 1974 Referendum (Box 13, Folder 2)
- Tellers, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 3)
- 1972 Referendum (Box 13, Folder 4)
- 1974 Convention (Box 13, Folder 5)
- Resolutions, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 6)
- Special Convention, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 7)
- Labor Summit- Inflation, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  September 11
- Summit Conference on Inflation, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 9)
- Summit Conference on Inflation, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 10)
- White House Labor Management Committee, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 11)
- White House Labor Management Committee, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 12)
- UNA Economic Policy Council, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 13)
- UNA Economic Policy Council, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 14)
- UNA Economic Policy Council, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 15)
- Industrial Ladies Garment Workers, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Health Maintenance Organization, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 2)
- Department of Labor Adjustment Assistance, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 3)
- Department of Labor: Labor Advisory Commission for Trade Negotiations, 1975-1976 (Box 14, Folder 4)
- Department of Labor: Labor Advisory Commission for Trade Negotiations, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 5)
- Department of Labor: Labor Advisory Commission for Trade Negotiations, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 6)
- Election 1976 (Box 14, Folder 7)
- Election 1976 (Box 14, Folder 8)
- ACTWU, 1974-1976 (Box 14, Folder 9)
- Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union Finances, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 10)
- Institute of Collective Bargaining and Group Relations Incorporated, 1976 (Box 15, Folder 1)
- Amalgamated Insurance Fund, 1976 (Box 15, Folder 2)
- Amalgamated Insurance Fund, 1976 (Box 15, Folder 3)
- Amalgamated Insurance Fund, 1976 (Box 15, Folder 4)
- Amalgamated Insurance Fund, 1976 (Box 15, Folder 5)
- Amalgamated Insurance Fund, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 6)
- Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America, 1976 (Box 15, Folder 7)
- Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America, 1972-1974 (Box 15, Folder 8)
- ACTWU, 1974-1974 (Box 15, Folder 9)
- ACTWU, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 10)
- ACTWU, 1972-1974 (Box 15, Folder 11)
- Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 12)
- Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America, 1974-1975 (Box 15, Folder 13)
- Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 14)
- International Trade and Investment on employment, 1976 (Box 15, Folder 15)
- International Trade and Investment on employment, 1976 (Box 15, Folder 16)
- Industrial Union Department, 1975-1976 (Box 15, Folder 17)
- Industrial Union Department, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 18)
- Labor for Peace, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 1)
- ACTWU- Legal Department, 1977 (Box 16, Folder 2)
- Legis 50, 1977 (Box 16, Folder 3)
- Labor Advisory Council, 1974 (Box 16, Folder 4)
- Labor Council for Latin American Affairs, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 5)
- Kurdish American Society for Refugee Relief, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 6)
- Kuppenheimer, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 7)
- Jobs Now Rally- Washington, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  April 26
- Jewish Labor Committee, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 9)
- Japanese Trip, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  June
- Japan Trip, 1974 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  January
- Jefferson Sportswear, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 12)
- Italian Relief, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 13)
- Israel, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 14)
- International Garment and Leather Workers Association, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 15)
- Insurance Company Status of Firms, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 16)
- Insurance Company Miscellaneous, 1972-1975 (Box 16, Folder 17)
- Insurance Company Financial Reports, 1972-1975 (Box 16, Folder 18)
- Legislative Matters, 1972-1975 (Box 16, Folder 19)
- Insurance Company Delinquencies Report, 1972-1974 (Box 16, Folder 20)
- Martin Luther King Center for Social Change, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 21)
- Labor Management Committee, 1977 (Box 16, Folder 22)
- Labor Management, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 23)
- Leonard Lewis, 1972 (Box 17, Folder 1)
- Levi-Strauss, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 2)
- Local 169, 1976-1973 (Box 17, Folder 3)
- Local 117, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 4)
- Local 752- Ashborn, Georgia, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 5)
- Marx and Haas, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 6)
- Mass transit, 1974 (Box 17, Folder 7)
- Mayor`s Office of Apparel Industry Planning and Development, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 8)
- Meetings of Clothing Managers, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 9)
- Meetings of Cotton Garment Managers, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 10)
- Golds Meir Luncheon, 1977 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  November 9
- Men`s Clothing Data, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 12)
- Metro, 1972 (Box 17, Folder 13)
- Milwaukee Joint Board, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 14)
- Minimum Wage, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 15)
- Minnesota Joint board, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 16)
- Montreal Joint Board, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 17)
- National coordinate Committee for Multi-employer Plan, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 18)
- National coordinate Committee for Multi employer Plan, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 19)
- National coordinate Committee for Multi employer Plan, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 20)
- National Economic Planning, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 21)
- National Health Insurance, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 22)
- National Health Insurance, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 23)
- National Health Insurance, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 24)
- National Planning Association, 1977 (Box 17, Folder 25)
- National Planning Association, 1976-1977 (Box 17, Folder 26)
- National Planning Association, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 27)
- National Planning Association, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 1)
- National Planning Association, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 2)
- Robert P Neudorf, 1973 (Box 18, Folder 3)
- New America, 1973 (Box 18, Folder 4)
- New Orleans Joint Board, 1973 (Box 18, Folder 5)
- New York Committee for Labor Youth, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 6)
- New York State Committee for National Health Security, 1975 (Box 18, Folder 7)
- Occupational Safety and Health, 1975 (Box 18, Folder 8)
- Outerwear, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 9)
- Philadelphia Joint Board, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 10)
- Philip Randolph Institute, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 11)
- Plant Closings, 1975 (Box 18, Folder 12)
- Pittsburgh Joint Board, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 13)
- President`s Advisory Committee, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 14)
- President`s Advisory Committee, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 15)
- President`s Advisory Committee, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 16)
- President`s Advisory Committee, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 17)
- Social Service Department, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 18)
- Social Service Department, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 19)
- Social Democrats USA, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 1)
- Puerto Rican Joint Board, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 2)
- Ratner California Clothes, 1975 (Box 19, Folder 3)
- Requests for Contractors, 1972 (Box 19, Folder 4)
- Research Department Reports, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 5)
- Research Department Reports, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 6)
- Research Department Reports, 1975 (Box 19, Folder 7)
- Robert Hall, 1975 (Box 19, Folder 8)
- Rochester Joint Board, 1973 (Box 19, Folder 9)
- Sears-Roebuck Company, 1973 (Box 19, Folder 10)
- Shirt and Leisurewear Joint Board, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 11)
- Sloan Commission, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 12)
- Sloan Commission, 1978 (Box 19, Folder 13)
- Sloan Commission, 1978 (Box 19, Folder 14)
- "A" General, 1983 (Box 19, Folder 15)
- African American Labor Center, 1982 (Box 19, Folder 16)
- Amalgamated Bank of New York, 1982-1983 (Box 19, Folder 17)
- Amalgamated Bank of New York, 1982-1983 (Box 19, Folder 18)
- Committee of Unemployed Members, 1983 (Box 19, Folder 19)
- Amalgamated Staff Retirement Plan, 1982-1983 (Box 19, Folder 20)
- American Jewish Committee, 1981-1983 (Box 19, Folder 21)
- Americans for Democratic Action, 1981-1983 (Box 19, Folder 22)
- Angelica Uniform Corp, 1982-1983 (Box 19, Folder 23)
- The Atlantic Monthly, 1981 (Box 19, Folder 24)
- United States Steering Committee, 1984 (Box 19, Folder 25)
- ABNY Executive Committee, 1983 (Box 19, Folder 26)
- Aspen Institute Bureaucracy Project, 1982-1983 (Box 20, Folder 1)
- American Productivity Center, 1983 (Box 20, Folder 2)
- American Productivity Center, 1982 (Box 20, Folder 3)
- Applications for Employment, 1982-1983 (Box 20, Folder 4)
- Asian American Free Labor Institute, 1982-1983 (Box 20, Folder 5)
- ACTWU Negotiations, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 6)
- ACTWU - Safety and health committee, 1984 (Box 20, Folder 7)
- Political Action Committee, 1982-1983 (Box 20, Folder 8)
- Asian American Labor Institute, 1982-1983 (Box 20, Folder 9)
- ACTWU- Referendum Election, 1984 (Box 20, Folder 10)
- ACTWU Staff, 1981-1984 (Box 20, Folder 11)
- ACTWU Retired Labor Leaders, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 12)
- Administratorships, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 13)
- COPE, 1982-1983 (Box 20, Folder 14)
- AFL-CIO, 1982-1984 (Box 20, Folder 15)
- AFL-CIO, 1982-1983 (Box 20, Folder 16)
- AFL-CIO Community Service, 1982 (Box 20, Folder 17)
- AFL-CIO Convention, 1983 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  October 2-6
- AFL-CIO 16th Convention, 1985 (Box 21, Folder 1)
- AFL-CIO, 1985 (Box 21, Folder 2)
- Department of Information, 1984 (Box 21, Folder 3)
- Industrial Union Department, 1984-1986 (Box 21, Folder 4)
- AFL-CIO Executive Council, 1986 (Box 21, Folder 5)
- AFL-CIO Executive Council, 1985 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  August
- AFL-CIO Executive Council, 1985 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  May 5-7
- AFL-CIO Executive Council, 1984 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  August 20
- AFL-CIO Executive Council, 1985 (Box 21, Folder 9)
- AFL-CIO Executive Council, 1984 (Box 21, Folder 10)
- AFL-CIO Executive Council meeting, 1984 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  February 20
- AFL-CIO Executive Council Meeting, 1983 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  August 8-10
- AFL-CIO Executive Council, 1983 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  May24-25
- AFL-CIO Executive Council, 1983 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  February 21-28
- AFL-CIO Executive Council, 1983 (Box 21, Folder 15)
- AFL-CIO Executive Council, 1982-1983 (Box 21, Folder 16)
- AFL-CIO Financial Statement, 1982-1983 (Box 21, Folder 17)
- AFL-CIO General Correspondence, 1982-1984 (Box 21, Folder 18)
- AFL-CIO Department of International Affairs, 1982-1983 (Box 21, Folder 19)
- AFL-CIO Executive Council, 1982 (Box 21, Folder 20)
- AFL- CIO Executive, 1982 (Box 22, Folder 1)
- AFL-CIO Hearing, 1978-1984 (Box 22, Folder 2)
- AFL-CIO Legislative Department, 1982-1984 (Box 22, Folder 3)
- AFL-CIO George Meany Center, 1982-1983 (Box 22, Folder 4)
- AFL-CIO Publications, 1982-1983 (Box 22, Folder 5)
- AL-CIO Rally, 1981 (Box 22, Folder 6)
- AFL-CIO Solidarity Day, 1983 (Box 22, Folder 7)
- Amalgamated Insurance Fund, 1982-1983 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  Financial Reports
- Amalgamated Insurance Fund, 1981-1983 (Box 22, Folder 9)
- Amalgamated Insurance Fund, 1982-1983 (Box 22, Folder 10)
- Amalgamated Insurance Fund, 1982 (Box 22, Folder 11)
- Amalgamated Insurance Fund, 1982-1983 (Box 22, Folder 12)
- Cotton Garment Insurance, 1983 (Box 22, Folder 13)
- Amalgamated Cotton Garment and Allied Industrial Fund, 1982-1983 (Box 22, Folder 14)
- AFL- CIO Statements, 1986-1985 (Box 22, Folder 15)
- AFL- CIO Statements, 1982-1984 (Box 22, Folder 16)
- AFL- CIO Statements, 1982-1983 (Box 22, Folder 17)
- AFL- CIO Statements, 1982 (Box 22, Folder 18)
- African American Labor Center, 1984-1985 (Box 22, Folder 19)
- Amalgamated Bank of New York, 1985 (Box 22, Folder 20)
- Amalgamated Bank of New York, 1985 (Box 23, Folder 1)
- Clofund, Alico, Clothing Fund Current Memberships, 1983 (Box 23, Folder 2)
- Amalgamated Department Store and Retail Employees Insurance Fund, 1985 (Box 23, Folder 3)
- Amalgamated Cotton Garment and Allied Industries Fund, 1985 (Box 23, Folder 4)
- Amalgamated Cotton Garment and Allied Industries Fund, 1986-1987 (Box 23, Folder 5)
- Amalgamated Cotton Garment and Allied Industries Fund, 1986 (Box 23, Folder 6)
- Amalgamated Cotton Garment and Allied Industries Fund, 1984 (Box 23, Folder 7)
- Amalgamated Cotton Garment and Allied Industries Fund, 1986 (Box 23, Folder 8)
- Amalgamated Cotton Garment and Allied Industries Fund, 1985 (Box 23, Folder 9)
- Amalgamated Insurance Fund, 1984-1987 (Box 23, Folder 10)
- Amalgamated Insurance Fund, 1985-1984 (Box 23, Folder 11)
- Amalgamated Insurance Fund, 1984 (Box 23, Folder 12)
- Amalgamated Insurance Fund, 1985 (Box 23, Folder 13)
- Amalgamated Insurance Fund, 1985 (Box 23, Folder 14)
- Amalgamated Life and Insurance Company, 1987 (Box 23, Folder 15)
- Amalgamated Life Insurance Company, 1985 (Box 23, Folder 16)
- Amalgamated Life Insurance Company, 1983 (Box 23, Folder 17)
- Amalgamated Life Insurance Company, 1983-1984 (Box 24, Folder 1)
- Amalgamated Staff Retirement Plan, 1986 (Box 24, Folder 2)
- Amalgamated Staff Retirement Plan, 1986 (Box 24, Folder 3)
- Amalgamated Washable Fund, 1986 (Box 24, Folder 4)
- The American assembly, 1986 (Box 24, Folder 5)
- American Civil Liberties, 1983 (Box 24, Folder 6)
- American European Community Association, 1984 (Box 24, Folder 7)
- American Israel Corporation-Ampal, 1984 (Box 24, Folder 8)
- Ampal-American Israel Corporation, 1983 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  May2-7
- American Labor ORT, 1986 (Box 24, Folder 10)
- Organization through rehabilitation through training, 1984 (Box 24, Folder 11)
- American productivity center, 1984 (Box 24, Folder 12)
- American productivity center, 1984 (Box 24, Folder 13)
- The Asia Society, 1983 (Box 24, Folder 14)
- Asian-American free labor institute, 1984 (Box 24, Folder 15)
- Amalgamated cotton garment and allied industrial fund- retirement- annual reports, 1977-1981 (Box 24, Folder 16)
- Amalgamated cotton garment and allied industrial fund- insurance- annual reports, 1976-1980 (Box 24, Folder 17)
- The Botto House American Labor Museum, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 18)
- Brazil Labor Information, 1984 (Box 24, Folder 19)
- Burlington Industries Incorporated, 1985 (Box 24, Folder 20)
- The Botto House, 1982 (Box 24, Folder 21)
- Boys` Town of Italy, 1983 (Box 24, Folder 22)
- Brookfield Clothes, 1980 (Box 24, Folder 23)
- Brookings Institute, 1980 (Box 24, Folder 24)
- Burlington Institute, 1982 (Box 24, Folder 25)
- New York Business/ Labor Group, 1981 (Box 24, Folder 26)
- Brazil Labor Information, 1981 (Box 24, Folder 27)
- Bilderberg, 1983 (Box 24, Folder 28)
  October 14-15
- Bilderberg Meeting, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  May 12-15
- Bilderberg Steering Committee, 1980 (Box 25, Folder 2)
- Bilderberg Meeting, 1981 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  May 15-17
- Bilderberg Meeting, 1982 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  October 22-23
- Bilderberg Conference, 1982 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  May 13
- Blood Bank, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 6)
- CLC Conference, 1982 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  May 24-28
- Center for International Affairs, 1983-1984 (Box 25, Folder 8)
- Center for National Policy, 1984 (Box 25, Folder 9)
- Churchill Computer, 1985 (Box 25, Folder 10)
- Carnegie Corporation, 1984 (Box 25, Folder 11)
- Carnegie Endowment for International Peace, 1987 (Box 25, Folder 12)
- Carnegie Melon University, 1986 (Box 25, Folder 13)
- Caron International, 1984 (Box 25, Folder 14)
- City of Hope- Sheinkman Award Dinner, 1986 (Box 25, Folder 15)
- City of Hope, 1986 (Box 25, Folder 16)
- Canadian Office, 1986 (Box 25, Folder 17)
- Can-Citizens Against Nuclear War, 1985 (Box 25, Folder 18)
- City University of New York, 1984 (Box 25, Folder 19)
- CMA -Clothing Manufacturers` Association, 1986 (Box 25, Folder 20)
- CMA -Clothing Manufacturers` Association, 1986 (Box 25, Folder 21)
- Clothing Negotiations, 1986 (Box 25, Folder 22)
- Clothing Negotiations, 1985 (Box 26, Folder 1)
- Clothing Negotiations, 1985 (Box 26, Folder 2)
- Clothing negotiations, 1985 (Box 26, Folder 3)
- Clothing negotiations, 1985 (Box 26, Folder 4)
- Clothing negotiations, 1985 (Box 26, Folder 5)
- Clothing negotiations, 1984-1985 (Box 26, Folder 6)
- Clothing Vice President Meeting, 1984 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  February 2
- Cone Mills, 1984 (Box 26, Folder 8)
- The Conference Board, 1985 (Box 26, Folder 9)
- Congressional Correspondence, 1984 (Box 26, Folder 10)
- Constitution- ACTWU, 1984 (Box 26, Folder 11)
- Priority Contribution, 1986 (Box 26, Folder 12)
- Priority Contribution, 1986 (Box 26, Folder 13)
- Priority Contribution, 1986 (Box 26, Folder 14)
- Council of Hemispheric Affair, 1983-1986 (Box 26, Folder 15)
- Cranston, 1985 (Box 26, Folder 16)
- Canadian Office-ACTWU, 1982 (Box 26, Folder 17)
- Priority Contribution, 1985 (Box 26, Folder 18)
- Priority Contribution, 1985 (Box 26, Folder 19)
- Priority Contribution, 1984 (Box 26, Folder 20)
- Convention, 1987 (Box 27, Folder 1)
- Convention- Hollywood, Florida, 1984 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  June 11-15
- Convention- Hollywood Florida, 1984 (Box 27, Folder 3)
- Convention Committee, 1984 (Box 27, Folder 4)
- Conway Mills, 1984 (Box 27, Folder 5)
- Clothing Negotiations, 1982 (Box 27, Folder 6)
- Clothing Negotiations, 1982 (Box 27, Folder 7)
- Coalition of Labor Union of Women, 1982 (Box 27, Folder 8)
- Center for Strategic and International Studies, 1982 (Box 27, Folder 9)
- Clothing Industry, 1982-1983 (Box 27, Folder 10)
- Clothing Manufacturer`s Association, 1982-1983 (Box 27, Folder 11)
- Citizen`s Against Nuclear War, 1979-1982 (Box 27, Folder 12)
- Communication Workers of America, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 13)
- The Conference Board, 1982-1983 (Box 27, Folder 14)
- ACTWU Convention, 1981 (Box 27, Folder 15)
  June 1
- ACTWU- Council on Foreign Relations, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 16)
- Crafted with Pride in USA, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 17)
- City of Hope, 1981 (Box 27, Folder 18)
- Civil Rights, 1981 (Box 27, Folder 19)
  October
- Citizen Energy Coalition, 1981 (Box 27, Folder 20)
- Citizens for Balanced transportation, 1980 (Box 27, Folder 21)
- Citizens Budget Commission, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 22)
- Cotton Garment Negotiations, 1979 (Box 27, Folder 23)
- Corbin Limited, 1981 (Box 28, Folder 1)
- 1983 Priority Contributions (Box 28, Folder 2)
- Cotton Garment negotiations, 1982 (Box 28, Folder 3)
- Cotton Garment negotiations, 1982 (Box 28, Folder 4)
- Cotton Garment negotiations, 1982 (Box 28, Folder 5)
- Clothing Negotiations, 1982 (Box 28, Folder 6)
- Outerwear Negotiations, 1979 (Box 28, Folder 7)
- Outerwear Negotiations, 1982 (Box 28, Folder 8)
- Priority Contributions, 1981 (Box 28, Folder 9)
- Priority Contributions, 1981 (Box 28, Folder 10)
- Priority Contributions, 1982 (Box 28, Folder 11)
- The Committee for the free world, 1981 (Box 28, Folder 12)
- Committee for future America, 1981 (Box 28, Folder 13)
- Communications department, 1983 (Box 28, Folder 14)
- Conference on economic progress, 1983 (Box 28, Folder 15)
- Conferences, 1983 (Box 28, Folder 16)
- Connecticut State - AFL-CIO, 1981 (Box 28, Folder 17)
- Consolidated food corporation, 1983 (Box 28, Folder 18)
- Committee for a democratic consensus, 1983 (Box 28, Folder 19)
- Committee for national security, 1982 (Box 28, Folder 20)
- Committee for economic development, 1981 (Box 28, Folder 21)
- Cluett, Peabody, and Company Incorporation, 1983 (Box 28, Folder 22)
- Cluett, Peabody, and Corporation, 1983 (Box 28, Folder 23)
- Coalition for Employment through exports, 1982 (Box 28, Folder 24)
- Coalition for strategic stability in middle east, 1981 (Box 28, Folder 25)
- Columbia University- corporate welfare system study, 1983 (Box 28, Folder 26)
- US Department of Commerce, 1982 (Box 28, Folder 27)
- Marvin Ciporen, 1982 (Box 28, Folder 28)
- Chicago world trade council, 1982 (Box 28, Folder 29)
- Chicago Federation of Labor, 1984 (Box 28, Folder 30)
- Chicago Bank, 1982-1983 (Box 28, Folder 31)
- Chester County Sportswear, 1983 (Box 28, Folder 32)
- David Chaney Memorial Project, 1982-1983 (Box 28, Folder 33)
- Champion Pants Company, 1982 (Box 28, Folder 34)
- CETA, 1981 (Box 28, Folder 35)
- National Clothing Agreement, 1974 (Box 28, Folder 36)
- Import Committee, 1980 (Box 28, Folder 37)
- Technology Committee, 1980 (Box 28, Folder 38)
- Council of Foreign Relations, 1980 (Box 29, Folder 1)
- Blue Cross, 1982 (Box 29, Folder 2)
- Center for Defense Information, 1982-1983 (Box 29, Folder 3)
- CBS Taping, 1982 (Box 29, Folder 4)
- Cavalier Clothes, 1983 (Box 29, Folder 5)
- Budgets, 1982 (Box 29, Folder 6)
- Canadian Manufacturer's`Agreement- Health Benefits, 1975 (Box 29, Folder 7)
- Dan River Company, 1984 (Box 29, Folder 8)
- Dunlop clothing, 1982-1983 (Box 29, Folder 9)
- Dunlop Clothing, 1982-1983 (Box 29, Folder 10)
- Dissent, 1984 (Box 29, Folder 11)
- Charles Stark Draper Library, 1985 (Box 29, Folder 12)
- Dues Information, 1985 (Box 29, Folder 13)
- Economic Policy Council, 1986 (Box 29, Folder 14)
- Economic Policy Institute, 1984 (Box 29, Folder 15)
- Economics, 1984 (Box 29, Folder 16)
- Economic Week, 1983 (Box 29, Folder 17)
- Eugene V Debs Awards Dinner, 1985 (Box 29, Folder 18)
- Eugene V Debs Foundation, 1986 (Box 29, Folder 19)
- Democracy Project, 1984 (Box 29, Folder 20)
- Department of State, 1984 (Box 29, Folder 21)
- Department of Trade and Commerce, 1984 (Box 29, Folder 22)
- Damon International, 1982 (Box 29, Folder 23)
- Darlington, 1980 (Box 29, Folder 24)
- Eugene V Debs Award Dinner, 1982 (Box 29, Folder 25)
- Eugene V Debs Awards Dinner, 1982 (Box 29, Folder 26)
- Eugene V Debs Foundation, 1982 (Box 29, Folder 27)
- Democratic National Committee, 1983 (Box 29, Folder 28)
- District Council 37, 1981 (Box 29, Folder 29)
- District 65, 1983 (Box 29, Folder 30)
- American Ditchley Foundation, 1983 (Box 29, Folder 31)
- Dunlop Study, 1977 (Box 29, Folder 32)
- Ditchley Foundation Conference, 1980 (Box 29, Folder 33)
- Drechsler and Leff, 1982 (Box 30, Folder 1)
- Dues Information, 1982 (Box 30, Folder 2)
- Dylex Limited, 1982 (Box 30, Folder 3)
- Decontrol of Natural Gas, 1982 (Box 30, Folder 4)
- Democratic Socialists of America, 1981 (Box 30, Folder 5)
- 1984 Election, 1984-1985 (Box 30, Folder 6)
- 1984 Election, 1984-1985 (Box 30, Folder 7)
- The Carolinas- 1984 Election (Box 30, Folder 8)
- El Salvador, 1986 (Box 30, Folder 9)
- Economic Policy Council, 1983 (Box 30, Folder 10)
- Economics, 1983 (Box 30, Folder 11)
- The economist, 1980 (Box 30, Folder 12)
- ACTWU- Education Department, 1983 (Box 30, Folder 13)
- Egyptian Textile Union, 1983 (Box 30, Folder 14)
- 1982 Election Campaign (Box 30, Folder 15)
- Exports of United States Bank Report, 1976 (Box 30, Folder 16)
- Economy of Nations, 1980-1983 (Box 30, Folder 17)
- Economy of Nations, 1980 (Box 30, Folder 18)
- El Salvador, 1983 (Box 30, Folder 19)
- Bill Elkuss Memorial, 1972 (Box 30, Folder 20)
  February 7
- Energy, 1980 (Box 30, Folder 21)
- Pennsylvania Congressman Allen Ertel `s Luncheon, 1982 (Box 30, Folder 22)
  April 16